[
  {
    "question": "What is Jayway commited to?",
    "optionA": "Measurable goals",
    "optionB": "Iteration",
    "optionC": "Client relationships",
    "optionD": "Assumptions",
    "answer": "Client relationships"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following companies is a Jayway partner?",
    "optionA": "Amazon Web Services",
    "optionB": "Facebook",
    "optionC": "IMB",
    "optionD": "Volvo",
    "answer": "Amazon Web Services"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following cities has a Jayway office?",
    "optionA": "Madrid",
    "optionB": "Malmö",
    "optionC": "Paris",
    "optionD": "New York",
    "answer": "Malmö"
  },

  {
    "question": "How many years has Jayway been in the business?",
    "optionA": "30",
    "optionB": "10",
    "optionC": "20",
    "optionD": "40",
    "answer": "20"
  },

  {
    "question": "How many projects and products has Jayway built?",
    "optionA": "More than 100",
    "optionB": "More than 900",
    "optionC": "More than 1200",
    "optionD": "More than 2500",
    "answer": "More than 1200"
  },

  {
    "question": "What ideas does Jayway share on their blog?",
    "optionA": "Tech and good practices ",
    "optionB": "Tech and food",
    "optionC": "Tech and insight ideas",
    "optionD": "Tech and organizing",
    "answer": "Tech and insight ideas"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following projects was developed by Jayway?",
    "optionA": "Bill pay",
    "optionB": "Billum pay",
    "optionC": "Telm pay",
    "optionD": "Telia pay",
    "answer": "Telia pay"
  },

  {
    "question": "Does Jayway have an Immersive Lab?",
    "optionA": "You betcha they do!",
    "optionB": "They wish...",
    "optionC": "No",
    "optionD": "I don't know",
    "answer": "You betcha they do!"
  },

  {
    "question": "What did Jayway develop in the Massive entertainment project?",
    "optionA": "A videogame",
    "optionB": "An advertisement",
    "optionC": "A high-quality website",
    "optionD": "A banking app",
    "answer": "A high-quality website"
  },

  {
    "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
    "optionA": "Alexander Graham Bell",
    "optionB": "Sir Isaac Newton",
    "optionC": "Leonardo Da Vinci",
    "optionD": "Albert Einstein",
    "answer": "Leonardo Da Vinci"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following represents Jayway's goal?",
    "optionA": "Personal growth",
    "optionB": "Business insights",
    "optionC": "Grow great digital mindst",
    "optionD": "Generating revenue",
    "answer": "Grow great digital minds"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following products has Jayway part taking in?",
    "optionA": "Resound reflief",
    "optionB": "Candy Crush",
    "optionC": "Lenovo's Dell",
    "optionD": "Touch bracelets",
    "answer": "Resound reflief"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which of the following companies belong to Jayway's family?",
    "optionA": "Future of Tech",
    "optionB": "Lifehacker",
    "optionC": "Hack a Day",
    "optionD": "Forever Geek",
    "answer": "Future of Tech"
  },

  {
    "question": "Which is a Jayway data principle?",
    "optionA": "Data as a business",
    "optionB": "Data as design",
    "optionC": "Data as a product",
    "optionD": "Data as itiration",
    "answer": "Data as a product"
  },

  {
    "question": "Is Jayway one of the coolest companies to work for?",
    "optionA": "For sure!",
    "optionB": "No way",
    "optionC": "Nope",
    "optionD": "I don't know",
    "answer": "For sure!"
  }
]
